# **Vincy Parmar**

invincyble1985@gmail.com / 9920277873 / 85, Adarsh Nagar, Collector Compound, Pali Naka, Bandra (West), Mumbai, Maharashtra

## **Summary**

I aspire to work in a creative and challenging work atmosphere demanding high levels of commitment and excellence to achieve a career growth path through continuous learning and improvement mode coupled with professional satisfaction.

Performance-oriented sales leader offering an exceptional record of achievement over 12 years career. Tenacious manager with a strategic and analytical approach to solving problems, bringing in customers, and accomplishing profit targets. Talented in identifying and capitalizing on emerging market trends and revenue opportunities.

#### Experience

# Assistant Manager, Business Development

engage4more • Mumbai, Maharashtra 08/2018 - 11/2020

- Assisting the business head in managing the day to day activities if the corporate outreach team (IP Team).
- Heading the IP Team (CTC and Brain Bout).
- Sorting the RPC data for effective calling by the agents.
- Increasing the value of current customers while attracting new ones.
- Training personnel and helping team members develop their skills.
- Handled additional projects to manage the business better:-
- Manage the hiring in liaising with the recruitments team (Recruitment + Training)
- · Vendor Management.

## **Business Development Executive**

engage4more • Mumbai, Maharashtra 04/2016 - 08/2018

- Managing the self target of acquiring new corporates depending on the business goals.
- lead generation in finding the RPC's.
- · Assisting the BDM in training and managing

## **Relationship Officer**

National Bank Of Ras Al Khaimah (RAK Bank) • Dubai, Dubai 06/2014 - 12/2014

- Providing general information on all the banking products, value, and pricing to prospective customers, Servicing customers with financial solutions face to face, via phone calls and email.
- Liaised with clients by phone, email, and text messages to meet client needs and define expectations.
- Upselling the customer, by creating a requirement thereby generating business volume and increase sales.
- Cross-selling the customer and coordinating with the product specialist and respective department.
- Attain individual sales target, play a pivotal role in achieving the department target.

# **Customer Service Representative/Call Center**

Tech Mahindra • Mumbai, Maharashtra 01/2012 - 05/2014

- Determining the needs of the customers and cross-selling to maximum profits.
- Maintaining a database for the customers and helping the department.
- Conducting daily briefings and helping the team to build the department.
- Fulfilling requests by clarifying desired information; completing transactions; forwarding requests.
- Enhancing the organization's reputation by accepting ownership for accomplishing new and different requests.
- Resolving problems by clarifying issues; researching and exploring answers and alternative solutions.
- Assisting new customer service executives and handling the team.

## **Customer Service Representative/Call Center**

FIS (E-Funds) • Mumbai, Maharashtra 04/2007 - 05/2011

- Customer care support for an American bank
- Dealing with all the banks in America to check the customer's history.
- · Analyzing customer's credit history and giving feedback to bankers.
- Helping the team leader in making daily reports.
- Assisting new customer service executives and handling the team.
- Offered advice and assistance to customers, paying attention to special needs or wants.

#### **Customer Relations Executive**

Joseph Opticians • Mumbai, Maharashtra 03/2006 - 04/2007

- This job involves handling the showroom, Collecting payment, and preparing daily sales reports.
- Serving the customers by determining requirements.
- Fulfilling client's requests and maintaining customer relationship.
- Also providing the cash and sales details to the manager by the end of each day.

#### **Education**

St Anne's High School • Mumbai, Maharashtra 03/2003

### Commerce

Rizvi College of Arts, Science & Commerce • Mumbai , Maharashtra 02/2006

# Languages

• English • Hindi • Marathi

Gujarati